futuresimple.com 2019-05-17

# Privacy Notice | Sell

### We're committed to the confidentiality and security of your personal information.

We’re committed to the confidentiality and security of your personal information. If you are the customer of one of our clients, you may not have heard of us. Still, there is nothing more important to us than our relationship with you. You may not know why we would have data about you in our system. We process data on behalf of companies with whom you have a relationship, with whom you have shared your data. In simple terms, you are a data subject, your service provider is a data controller (who determines how your data can be processed) and we act as a data processor. We’re committed to the confidentiality and security of any personal information that has been provided to us about you. This Privacy Notice explains how we protect your rights and care for your information. It also describes:

  * Who we are
  * What we do as a company
  * Who are our clients
  * Why you may not have heard about us
  * The type of data we process
  * How we obtain data about you
  * Use of the Platform
  * What we do in conducting our business
  * Our use of cookies
  * Ads and Third Parties
  * What we require of our clients
  * Third parties with whom we share your data and why
  * Disclosures of Personal Data
  * EU – U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss - U.S. Privacy Shield
  * Data transfers
  * Assuring your rights
  * Marketing opt-out preferences
  * Social Media widgets
  * Blogs
  * Links to 3rd Party Sites
  * Testimonials
  * Collection and use of 3rd Party Information
  * Single Sign-On
  * Imported contacts
  * Security and protection of your data
  * Children’s Personal Information
  * Data Processing Agreement
  * Changes to this policy
  * Who to contact with any requests, concerns, or complaints

###### Who we are

Zendesk Sell (“The Service”) online services and the web site [https://getbase.com](https://getbase.com/) are provided by FutureSimple Inc. (“The Company”). We are based in San Francisco, CA, US.

###### What we do as a company

We are a provider of sales tools, customer relationship tools, and analytics that empower our clients to better serve their customers.

###### Who are our clients

We are a processor. Our tools and services are used by the companies that serve you. We work with companies of all sizes, in all industries around the world.

###### Why you may not have heard about us

Individuals do not use our services directly. Whether an employer, or a business working with other businesses as their customers, or a business working with consumers directly, companies need and gather information to better serve their clients. These companies use our platform to hold, analyze and get the most from the information they collect.

###### The type of data we process

Each client uses data differently. What is common to most is that they compile data that helps them better relate to you and provide services. Such information may include:

  * contact information and preferences
  * specific requirements you may have or interests you have expressed
  * preference as to how your service provided may contact you and how frequently
  * information you may have shared in conversations, emails, meetings
  * information about the type, frequency and volume of business you have done together
  * financials
  * location of data and demographics
  * competitive data
  * data that may be sensitive. Your service provider’s use of any such sensitive data requires your explicit consent

###### How we obtain data about you

We don’t typically collect information directly from individuals. Our clients gather information about their customers or employees and then upload that data onto our platform (either directly or by using the assistance of a third party) where they can benefit from the tools and services we provide. Of course, there are exceptions to this rule:

  * we collect information about our client representatives at sign up or login
  * we collect technical device information and addresses using cookies and similar technologies
  * we analyze and capture behaviors of individuals using our platform for analytics purposes only
  * we use the platform as an internal resource to manage employee and prospect data
  * we capture event data in logs, tracking systems and service tickets
  * we monitor and analyze access, traffic, performance and platform activity

###### Use of the Platform

Clients determine how they will use the platform for the processing of the data they collect. Each may differ in the services they elect to purchase and activate, whether there are customizations, and whether any analytic or third-party integrations will be used. Our client is bound by the terms of their own agreement with us and must also comply with all applicable laws in the proper and legitimate use of your data on Our platform.

###### What we do in conducting our business

  * conduct processing requests including analytics on behalf of our (data controller) clients
  * operate and develop our services;
  * send information, e.g. invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support messages
  * enhance client experience in the use of our services
  * inform clients and prospective clients about our other products or services (with their consent)
  * develop new products, integrations and services
  * distribute surveys
  * respond to comments and questions and provide customer service
  * protect against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activities

###### Our use of cookies

We use cookies to provide services on our platform. These cookies vary in purpose. Some are necessary for the basic functionality of the site, while others help provide an optimal experience, or help improve our services. Cookies are a choice, and the types of cookies you permit can be set as a preference, and those you choose not to allow are easily disabled. Outside of the Services, third parties and advertisers may also introduce cookies to your browser for their own needs and purposes which we do not control.

  * Cookies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user’s movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user community.
  * We use cookies for remembering users’ settings on our website, authentication to our shopping cart, and to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference)
  * Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.
  * If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
  * As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We do this to protect data and systems, improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, and site functionality.

###### Ads and Third Parties

We partner with a third-party ad network to either display advertising on our web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.

  * Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other web sites. They provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you do not wish to have your information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: [http://preferences-mgr.truste.com](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). You will continue to receive generic ads. In the EU, you may use the EDAA opt-out tool: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).
  * We use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site. When you view or click on an advert, a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.
  * We use mobile analytics software that may record information such as how often you use the application, events within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application.

###### What we require of our clients

We and our clients partner in assuring that your rights are protected. We require through our terms of service, that, as a condition of use of our platform, all clients fully adhere to applicable laws for your protection and the use of your data. You can view our terms of service at <https://getbase.com/terms/>.

The Company may transfer personal information for processing by other companies that help us provide our service. The Company uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, emailing, networking, storage, and related technology required to run The Service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. The use of third parties are governed by the provisions in this policy regarding notice and choice, and the service agreements with our clients.

Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to or from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our web site. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties and not to [https://getbase.com](https://getbase.com/).

###### Disclosures of Personal Data

The Company will not sell personally identifiable information, rent it, or exchange it with any third party. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. The Company uses the information collected to service you, bill you and perform research regarding the usage of The Service.

However, if requested by law, The Company holds its right to share your information with the authorities; as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

###### EU – U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss - U.S. Privacy Shield

Future Simple Inc. and its subsidiary company Base Sp. z o.o. participate in and has certified its compliance with the EU – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Future Simple Inc. is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

Future Simple Inc. is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Future Simple Inc. complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Company is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Future Simple Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

###### Data transfers

Transfers outside of the EU or to countries not deemed adequate in the protection of personal data are disallowed without explicit informed consent and an approved legal mechanism for transfer. We have certified under both the US and Swiss Privacy Shield agreements to facilitate transfer, and will use other appropriate legal transfer mechanisms as documented in our Data Processing Agreement.

###### Assuring your rights

Notice to End-Users Our Services are intended for use by enterprises. Where our Services are made available to you through a client of ours, that enterprise is the data controller of your personal information. Your data privacy questions and requests should initially be submitted to our subscribers in their capacity as your data controller. We are not responsible for our subscribers’ privacy or security practices which may be different than this Policy.

Our subscribers are able to:

  * restrict, suspend or terminate your access to the Services;
  * access and describe your personal information that you provided to them;
  * access and export your personal information processed by them; and
  * amend your personal information, including your end-user profile.

For all other users of our Services

GDPR assures that the rights and intentions of every individual regarding their personal data are respected. Any individual can request to access the data we hold about them, ensure it is current, correct and complete, and if the individual provided consent for that data to be processed, can revoke that consent freely. Individuals can also request that specific data held about them be updated, modified or deleted, or that all data about them be forgotten or ported. Individuals can make decisions regarding marketing preferences and the movement and transfer of their data. Exercise of these rights can be made by request to: [sell@zendesk.com](mailto:sell@zendesk.com) or by using the following web page – <https://support.getbase.com/hc/en-us/requests/new>.

###### Marketing opt-out preferences

The Company will use the email provided in the registration process to send a welcome email, billing and invoice information, and news and updates.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page, or you can contact us.

We will also send you service related email announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not promotional in nature.

If you choose to use our invite Teammates to our Service, we will ask you for that Teammate’s email address. We will automatically send a one-time email inviting that Teammate to use the Service. The Company stores this information to validate authorized users. Invited Teammates may contact us at [sell@zendesk.com](mailto:sell@zendesk.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ‘Share This’ button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

###### Blogs

Anytime you post on our blog please be aware that you are posting using a third-party application and we have no access or control over this information. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, you can either log into the third-party application to remove your comment, or you can contact the appropriate third-party application. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

###### Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our site includes links to other sites whose privacy practices may differ from the Company. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

###### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our web site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [sell@zendesk.com](mailto:sell@zendesk.com).

###### Collection and use of 3rd Party Information

There may be specific activities or reasons for which you may provide personal information about other people, such as their name, email address and phone number. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request and for completing the service for which the information was provided.

###### Single Sign-On

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Sign in with Google or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign-up form. Services like Sign in with Google give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

###### Imported contacts

You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our web site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import from your contacts and will only use it solely for that purpose.

###### Security and protection of your data

Our company has a robust security program and policy, leverages the expertise and security resources of our partners when in the cloud, and a program and policy for incident response. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number and/or geo-location data on our order forms or use the Service, we encrypt the transmission of information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our site, please contact us at [sell@zendesk.com](mailto:sell@zendesk.com) or +1 (855) 976-9550.

###### Children’s Personal Information

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through our Websites or Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide personal information through the Websites or Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us through the Websites or Services, please contact us at [sell@zendesk.com](mailto:sell@zendesk.com), and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information.

###### Data Processing Agreement

We have updated a Data Processing Agreement (DPA), as required under GDPR. If you require a signed DPA, as part of your GDPR compliance you can [download the agreement here](https://resources.getbase.com/hubfs/base-data-processing-agreement.pdf). Sign and complete the DPA with Company details and send the agreement to [sell-dpa@zendesk.com](mailto:sell-dpa@zendesk.com) to be countersigned by Sell.

###### Changes to This Policy

The Company may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. In any case of a significant change in the way personal information is used that is outlined in this Privacy Policy, we will alert the primary account owner via email prior to the change becoming effective. We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

###### Who to contact with any requests, concerns, or complaints

It is our hope that we would have the opportunity to cure any concerns that you may have regarding our site, your rights, and the care of your data by contacting us. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this web site or your dealings with this web site, please contact us using the information below:

Zendesk  
1019 Market Street, San Francisco, CA 94103  
+1 (650) 561-4871

It is the right of the individual to bring grievances regarding the protection and handling of their personal data to the Supervisory Authorities which can be reached at the following address: <https://www.giodo.gov.pl/en/323>.

Policy effective November 13, 2018
